8likes.com 2011-11-28

# 8Likes - Best Daily Deals

8Likes cares about your privacy and takes it very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the 8Likes website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

What does this Privacy Policy cover? 

This Privacy Policy covers 8Likes treatment of personal information that 8Likes gathers when you are on the 8Likes website and when you use 8Likes services. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that 8Likes does not own or control, or to individuals that 8Likes does not employ or manage. 

What personal information about users does 8Likes collect? 

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a friendly, customized, and efficient experience. We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with the purpose for which it has been collected or subsequently authorized by you. 

8Likes collects personally identifying information during the registration process, including name, email address, etc. 8Likes also may, on occasion collect user preference information (such as items clicked from emails), to be used for internal research purposes. We may also store information users knowingly provide such as feedback forms, suggestions, and emails to the 8Likes website. 8Likes may use such information for its internal purposes, including, but not limited to, email and web design optimizations, new features, and editorial and feedback purposes. Information entered may be aggregated across all users in order to determine and target demographics for marketing and advertising purposes. 

All user information stored by 8Likes is considered confidential and will not be shared with outside parties. 8Likes may share aggregated results of preferences for all users for marketing and advertising purposes. 

If you object to such use for any reason, you can either let us know by sending us feedback, or you can unsubscribe from the 8Likes email service. 

Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously. While 8Likes will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available. 

What about cookies? 

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. 8Likes cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or email address is. 

The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of 8Likes' most attractive features. 

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our website (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

Will 8Likes share any of the information it receives? 

Information about our users is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone. We share your personal information only as described below. 

Protection of 8Likes and others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with that law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of 8Likes, our employees, our users, or others. 

With your consent: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your personal information may be shared with third parties or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, and you will be able to prevent the sharing of this information by opting out. 

Is information about me secure? 

Your 8Likes account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to work to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by logging off once you have finished using a shared computer. 

Links to Other Sites 

8Likes uses links to guide you toward valuable products, services and editorial. We are not responsible for any content that appears on these sites, nor do we endorse them. For questions about these sites, please consult their individual privacy policies. 

Age Appropriate Content 

8Likes is not intended for use by children, especially those under age 13. No one under age 13 is allowed to use the site, provide any personal information or receive our email distributions. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s)or legal guardian(s) before viewing the website or receiving emails. 

How do I Unsubscribe? 

To unsubscribe, click on the unsubscribe link in any 8Likes email. You will be taken to a confirmation page. Click on the confirm link and you will be unsubscribed. 

Conditions of use 

If you decide to visit 8Likes website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of North Carolina state law. 

If you have any other questions about our privacy policy, shoot an email to privacy@8Likes.com. 

Modifications to Privacy Policy 

8Likes reserves the right to change this policy from time to time, however, all changes will be posted to this Privacy Policy at the time such changes are made. The date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page so please check back. Please note that continued access of 8Likes will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy. 

If you have concerns or questions about any aspect of the 8Likes Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at privacy@8likes.com. We welcome your questions and feedback. 

Last modified: May 26, 2011
